I don't know, I think, hold on.
Saman.
I know, Saman.
They can click I said don't I said don't say names don't say names you just said a person then you're like giving me
No names and you're saying it's not I don't care if it's not about it's doxing if you're you're getting people's names
And especially if you're talking about people these people like they like to find any little thing they can strike for okay?
Just but I told the don't say like if you don't do that to me then don't say anybody's name
I don't just don't mention people that don't mention that what is it gonna do?
It takes all the argument away
They're just gonna get mad and and then say and screw my channel it keeps I can't keep ending it
I asked you I was like stops. There's a no it's like and I said I don't care if it's no doc and you still did it anyway
Okay, don't just don't say names
And I don't care as a nickname
They're looking to, I don't know, they're trying to bait you to do stuff like that, okay?
Don't do it.
You're falling to their trap and then all it's going to do is hurt my channel.
It's like they're not, they're not, you want to talk, talk, just go say that to them on
your channel, okay?
Say that to them on your channel.
That's insane on my channel. I was in you have a discussion. You can make your points without doing what they do
You're two being to their level. Okay
It's annoying
Keep having to fucking delete streams
No one's gonna time you out and
Same as not gonna time you up, but you didn't do it. I mean just because you disagree. I don't think he has any problem with you, but
you know
and Jan is like, you know
No, I don't know. There's a dick. There's there's a distinction between the
The n-word with the stop like the soft a and the heart are I know it's stupid. I know it doesn't make sense
I know it sounds
Ridiculous the problem is even the word the problem is they get against the TOS to say the heart like to the heart are right?
And then people can flag and say oh, you know hate. Hey, there's hate speeches. They're saying the n-word on this channel, right?
Soft a I don't know. Hold on
You I'm not giving them power salmon. I'm trying. I'm working this out. Okay. Okay. I don't like the heart are either
And that's when people form and people I'm trying to follow strict guidelines. No one cares
Oh, hold on. Just give me a minute. I don't want to do I don't want to it's like what why do I keep?
I this is not what this shows about like oh, let's have you know
Let's let's have another day focused on Gotti and JT and then everyone arguing about
Dox and then it's just it's just
I don't like it. I don't, I don't want it, like, if it's not the right channel for it, I don't see any, are you doing, are you contributing?
So, I mean, they're like, Goddy and they're not really saying much in chat than they sent a snarky comments or, yeah.
I can't now I have to like not have people in the panel at the same time people have to you know, wait back
And then they'll go oh, I'm waiting make sure you cut him on like guys. I wrote my panel like I want to okay, so
He'll protect by violating TOS repeatedly. Hold on. I'm violating TOS or stuff that comes out of people's mouth
But I'm telling them not to say right in the moment that they keep saying
Is that it or no or other people posting photos of other people with you know, and I have to end the stream
Is that so how am I violating TOS? I mean, I just want to know that okay
Yeah, the people who claim to be protecting your channel keep violating TOS repeatedly
Right. It seems to me if they've respected you or the channel, they would keep certain words and things out of their mouth. I
Know and I keep saying don't and there's rules and everything but I say it and if you need to know better. I don't know
How about we talk about something how about we
Coins the palette and we talk about something that doesn't have anything to do with Sam man
What about that?
or JT and Gotti or anything that hurts anybody's feelings.
Yeah, I prefer just like, you know, this is a...
I mean, it's like, I mean, there's certain people...
It's just like, it's a 10th stream tonight, yeah, I know.
It's like, yeah, yeah, I know it's a great thing, Justin.
I wanted to I was I was trying to work that there's some good points we made but then it's just as it de-escalates into like
nonsense name-calling and
Doxy and then it's like in the politics also for all the then everyone's saying the n-word at once and it's like, you know
It's bad enough. He's saying it now. Everyone's saying okay, so
Please it's like just because I
I can tell not to say it, but I can't like change
I actually don't have a problem with that word. It's one of my favorite words to use
But I can't really upset with people. I I don't get really upset with people. I hate hypocrisy
So if I'm not allowed to use that word
In my descriptive in my descriptions of some people then they're not also allowed to use that word
Yeah, just because they have melanated skin, right? Right? Yeah, my problem isn't the word either
It's like, you know, it's I don't
What like or use the word but the problem is not the word the problem is against to us
I'm a monetized channel right people are trying to swag every little thing and so I
Can only tell people so much some of some people isn't they're vernacular
They say it every other word and it's just like, you know, that's just how they are
And I don't I don't I know there's double standards about it. I think but
I can't tell him don't say it go easy on the word go easy on us like stop
But until he can I don't like how people be like oh, but he did it
Oh, but he did this but he did that you know like trying to like compromise of what they did like take responsibilities for your actions
You said it you did it don't blame it. Oh, but this guy did this and you let him rock stop it
Stop the camp because the thing is like i'm not so i'm not like no one's supposed to use it
But but is the only alternative if someone does and everyone's supposed to use it like no, it's like
No, it's against the rules, and I'll have to be harder on people in the panel, take
people off if they don't, if I say stop saying that and they keep saying it, but it's annoying.
I don't know why people are bringing other people's names.
I don't know these other people.
They're not involved.
They're not in the show.
They're not here to defend themselves.
I don't know anything about it.
I don't want to bring this drama here.
And it's like, that's all that's happening.
And so it's, I have to like, you know,
not have certain people on the panel.
It's like, I mean, they seem to like have zeroed
in on the show.
Like it's like, like, what, they don't, don't like me.
All right.
Saki, just thought right in my head.
Try try you could try right? I'm just saying not telling you what to do
You could try to see how it is without those certain people's on the panel for like a couple days or a week and then
Try to see how different it is when you let them back on the panel for a day. Oh, you know, you know, I'm saying I'm just saying
That doesn't work. That doesn't work for every equation because different people bring a mix to every every different scenario
So one person
Well we go to and see how it is keep the panel good
But here's the thing but here's the thing about being a panel host
I know I've done it before it's it gets really fucking hard and everybody's screaming to you
You know to do this. I know trust me
Jen I'm a panel host too. I had my own a1 community
Lives always every weekend almost every day. I was like psyche. It was like that
It was going live every day going to her I um do my a1 thing and then I host a live at night time
and I had chose just the same way and I figured it out just the same way I'm explained so if it worked for me
I'm just you know throwing it out there to see if it could work for him a week without the trouble makers a week with
The trouble makers realize the difference
Yeah, I mean it's like yeah, it's like you know and and I know people are gonna they're gonna start
Scream, they're gonna get so upset. It's like, you know, like if I don't bring people in the panel to get mad
If I take him up for 10 seconds to give him and it's a I it's like I know they'll get mad and that many start
Can't make anybody happy so you just don't make your own decision
No, I'm making decision I don't give a shit what any of you think and that's me and fuck it. Yeah
And don't let me yesterday. I was like, yo, you had a you had a panel going for three hours
No poem bomb success and I realized like some of your panels go real good without certain people once they get there
You have to end it or something because that that group of people just messes it up
Yeah, and it's like a minute. It's like it and this has happened so many times
It must be like something intentional because
I mean, it's like I'm doing so many there's only so many times I can explain so many
It's I don't know. It's like it's just and it seems like they're just getting off on it
Like and then then they play big. Oh, oh, well, you know, he's like, well, why aren't why why did why?
Weren't they getting timed out for that? I never noticed anyone docking anything about anything about him
I'm not not once and it's like I don't know if I miss it in chat. I don't but my mom
I think J.T. was really just trying to have a conversation with you.
I don't think he has any agendas or motives like he was really just trying to have an analytical conversation about why is it this way for some people and why is it not.
The reality is it is always going to be that way because every stream owner has their preferences, every stream owner has people that they like or know more than the new people.
feel like that's that's not a that's not an equation that can ever get solved
because it changes with every variable person that you add into the equation
these are people that are like you have to appreciate people individually they
like yeah they'd like chaos they're they like
Taking the show off track. They like they they like when I get
Poor bomb and they like when I in the street
You know, it's like they liked when I was the all these trolls came in last night and it was just chaos on the panel and
Stammy celebrated when you took the stream down. Yeah, they celebrate
Yeah backstage and people see if people watching they can see backstage and doing it
They can't see the people like can see them, but people are there watching. Okay?
And yeah, Samman is a menace, he actually is.
I have to shake that guy.
No, he's a successful, you know, popular stream.
And, you know, he kind of does that kind of content,
more of that content.
So that's more appropriate, like, you know,
have these discussions kind of on a panel like his,
where he kind of embraces that kind of drama.
I'm trying to...
Bring people together. I'm trying to like have a nice show
I'm trying to have a place where you know everybody can go and it's like and not feel uncomfortable and it's like unfortunately
So many people have been chased off the show so many normal people that come that you know could could be potential people that you know
Come fans of the show and subscribers. They just they run they run away when they see what's going on the chat in the panel
Sometimes yeah, I'm not even a lot early. I wanted to join but I left because it was it was the drama was coming in once
I seen whooping them. I'm not going back up there. I know it's gonna be drama something's gonna happen
And I was gonna answer
Yeah, and it's like, you know, it's important. It's important to recognize and from what I see and I know that you guys don't really see
this side of it because
You only see JT and Gotti coming here, but
I see them other places too. They're not just running around trying to create hat like create have it
They join a panel and these people come to them and start harassing them
I want whatever panel they're at, or wherever they're hanging at.
It takes two to tango.
It takes two to tango is that, you know, it's like, there's, it's very easy to block people
in chats and to like, or not acknowledge them, ignore them if they think they're being told
you'd bring her up.
Hey, Rusty's here!
Rusty!
Hi, Rusty.
Yeah, so.
I love Rusty.
Yeah, she's cool.
She was on the panel earlier.
Um, for a really nice person, you know.
She is.
She's a beautiful soul.
Yeah.
And there, I met, I think they brought, um, good people here.
I love uh, I'm sorry
The lady earlier, I'm so sorry
She was the lady was here a little bit really blondly. She was she's just so sweet. I'm just free in her nickname, but
Okay, so she's awesome and you know you're awesome and you're awesome and I think you were here before for them
But you know then you know platform boots rusty school. I have no problem with people that come and are
positive and stuff and are not involved in some of the and it's like I
understand like you know you can be friends and like nothing the friends
are doing that and that's like but you don't people are not you but you know
other people don't do that like it's really too difficult I can't really sort
it all out the month I don't expect my mom to go and figure this all out it's
just like I'd rather just like not have it right it's like but it's like
You know, it's there seem to determine to something and they're like, oh, yeah, like what does they they said?
Oh, how about we clap psyche someone said hey, how do we clap psyches channel or how do we clap psyche in the
And they're like, yeah, let's do it. There's things like that in the chat
Like oh, why are you talking about clapping my channel? It means it means striking it
It means and what and God you saying oh
This channel is going down the night the night that God struck psyches channel blah blah blah. It's like
No, he's just messing with you. That's just not got any message. I know it does. I know it
This is very serious. It's like, you know, it's like, you know going into somebody's job and they say oh
I'm gonna talk to the manager. Have you fired and it's like or and it's like well
That's that's only it's only threatening to my job. It's not like funny. It's not not like a joke
Don't know maybe it's funny to them, but is that all they're it's like really humor is not just
I don't think it's malicious is what I'm trying to say
Well, they put they've been putting up pictures
Yeah, and I hear other story. I mean, it's like I know I can't like that's a view of your story
But I hear from reputable people. Hey these people they like to go around
To different panels and they do a lot of doxing and they talk to all these people
they're fighting with people and then
They ruin eventually ruin the channel ruin the panel
Either everyone stops coming in or it's just their group or it's and then or then
It just devolves into like it starts getting strikes because the ball the doxin and stuff
So I just need to like you know top of it. I can't just like let myself be under tech
It's like I'm letting people into the panel
It's like letting people into the house and it's like if they start
You know kicking out a furniture demanding things and like oh feed me this be me this be me this right then
like I'm like well who are you like what like did you bring you know did you bring
like a like a bottle of wine or something to the party are you you know
you're here to participate or it's like you're just here to like come in it
trash the place and then just go on to the next place and laugh and laugh and
while I'm cleaning up all the all the pieces picking up the pieces right it's
like
It's not it's not funny. It is it feels malicious. I have a feeling I get feelings people get feelings
I mean everyone's saying it
They keep they kept and they have stopped like I asked them several times. They kept posting
pictures of a cancer scar
Videos of disabled minors and I mean it's like nothing. I want to be involved. I can't I can't it's not the shows about
I keep explaining it and they keep doing it and it's like and then oh
He begs for a mod and then you know, he was one of his mother. I just need my mom
So I don't that guy don't ever give that guy mod. He's a leech. He's a roach step on in every time you see him
That's the only way to get rid of that dude
He actually is malicious. He has very malicious intent and you'll fuck your shit up any time you get the chance with his stupid
chaotic nonsense. Yeah, I mean I say, he has the, his, his, his, his avatar is a, is a Goetia demon and they're, all they are are these
demons of mischief, chaos and, and, uh,
low level, low level fuckhead demons. Yeah. Yeah. I'm familiar. It's not, it's not even a king. It's a low level demon. Yeah.
Tim and you in the chat over there acting like a five-year-old talking about I smell first of all
You ain't ever getting close enough to catch a whiff second of all
Grow up
Yeah, I'm talking to adults and talk to adults
Like another adult
You smell are you five? Are you five?
Who who do you think that's gonna bother? I know it was it's like it's very I mean all like a lot of it gets very
it involves into like a
Like a playground. It's like not even like you know, it's not even like high school. It's like it's like
It's like they're like crazy kids on on Ritalin or something like that, I mean it's like
Okay, so
We can have a discussion so JT's in the back so
So yeah, okay, so we should bring him on. What do you guys think? I'm all I always vote for JP. I love dude
I think he's great. Okay
Easy, what do you think?
I'm listening to y'all. I don't want to interrupt
Yeah, he's in the back
Okay, I won't put you guys in the spot. Okay. I'll just bring
But if you feel like you want to bring them up bring them up. That's just your pain. It's like I gotta hold it down
I gotta make a decision of whether to stay or not, but it'll matter. Okay. You can have a discussion
You can have a discussion because I need to I need some closure in this. I just I'm not just gonna like
Just do an outright ban. But you know, it's getting close. It's getting to the point. Hey
It's it's taking away. It's the
Taking away too much from the show all all this stuff. It's like too much
Am I bringing it to you or people bringing it to you? It was never happened before you guys came
I mean it has happened and right, but am I doing anything to you?
Well, I don't I don't I don't I don't necessarily know because there's stuff going on and no
I mean, I'm asking like a very straightforward. I've I always been respectful to you
It's in my face
Perhaps when I know you haven't been you said I was weak. You told me
Would you rather me say that behind your back or just say you're saying PDF stuff?
And then you're complaining that you got timed out and why isn't other people caught time up for stuff
I don't even know about they're saying
Someone's I don't think Gotti said psyche file and they're just putting there's a putting
Stamman file and they're you know, they're just
You're very quick to notice that but you're not quick to notice anybody mentioning my name because I told you I told you at that time
I was on a more high alert because the chat was really weird yesterday
And so I went I went off the panel and I focused completely on the chat
So I thought I was watching the chat. I'm not holding any grudges against you man. I know
I don't feel like arguing about this
for weeks and weeks and weeks and weeks.
I do, I do.
It's fine.
Either come here, come here, like chill on the panel,
have a nice conversation, ask for a chair reading.
That's what I do.
Or just don't come.
It's like, I don't want you fighting with all the chat.
I don't want you, it's like you're just gonna bring
all this chaos and then it's gonna be, you know,
threats made and there's gonna be doxing
and then it's like, it'll all come to my channel.
It's not gonna harm anybody else.
It's not gonna settle anything between you
and you, you're gonna fight with these people forever.
You're never gonna settle it.
You're starting my channel by your behavior. Okay by your behavior by putting those photos up. I asked you not to put it up
You put it up
No, you're doing photos on your on your avatar and stuff and God and all you guys were doing it
Okay, and so in yes that can then and you did it to that guy too that was on I forgot that got Yarl or something
He came in he's like he's about to strike my channel. He's like, but I saw that you were like don't put that
I never put his picture up. He's lying
Well, I don't know if you did it or somebody else did but he said
Okay, I can't necessarily go cross-reference. I am I kind of take no no one at the time said oh, that's not true in the chat
The he said no, it's whatever anybody says about me. It's got to be true. I got you. Okay. Well, whatever whatever if I choose to believe it
It's my decision. Okay. Why do you have authority here? You have no authority or your power here Satan, okay?
I'm the god of this world. I'm the god of this panel
you listen to me if you want to be on this panel. You're not here because it's a right to be here.
You're here because it's my show and I'm bringing you on, but I don't really feel like having you
on anymore. You cause more and more problems than you're worth and you're ruining my show.
So you're not going to fucking ruin my show. You're not going to mess with my baby. You're
sitting here causing all this problem. I'd rather just ban you from the panel and from the chat
if I want to. It's my decision and all of you guys, if you cause problems.
You're here upsetting everybody people are leaving but like all my most of my mods most of my mods like 90% of them are like
What the fuck is going on?
I mean I hear what you guys do. I know I know there's some good
You're good people in your group and there's different
They you know it's a different thing
But it's like you guys are stirring up shit trying to cause problems for my channel and it's like or even if you're not
You're going after people on my channel, which is like reflect battery reflects on my platform, right? And then it's like
And it's like, I know I have to figure this out and have to run it better, right?
But yeah, I'm not going to be weak.
I will just ban your ass if you keep this up.
It's like, stop whining about things.
Just, you know, if you get banned from the chat, you get banned from the chat.
If a mod bans you, a mod bans you.
There's other channels that their mods have the power to ban sometimes.
My mods usually don't even ban.
They just time over 24 hours.
It's a very liberal policy.
I have channels I love that I've
I was there for months. I was the mod there. I was a huge donor that have just banned me outright on ten accounts
Okay, and it's like what?
Am I gonna complain? It's like no. It's just oh, okay. I guess they don't want me there. Why are you so determined to go?
He like here. I don't know like go do it somewhere else. I thought I told you this is not a show for
you to air your personal grievances with
These people I don't know my right or my wrong. I see the chat Sam. I had the emotional pressure. Okay, I feel I feel
You stood up for yourself and you're not having it ten toes down congratulations
That's great. All that's great. Are we having a conversation or am I just being talked at like it's cool
No, no, no, I got I said what I had to say you can reply now
I'm not interested in controlling your channel or ruining your channel psych
I never have I've always been respectful with you if people if you compare how often I'm brought up to you as
Opposed to how often I bring up any anybody else to you. You'd see an obvious difference
I'm not bringing anybody up to you ever about anything. I
Can't
Up to me is that like they're like, oh, he's using the picture again. He's posting that link again
You know, it's not even true at the time. It's not even true. I don't know
Guys listen, I have mods here that have been here for a long time, you know
Thank you, Amanda. Thank you so much for the super sticker. Thank you so much
Here's Rusty Rusty
Rusty hi, hi during the conversation
What are you thinking about things
I don't know. I don't know what the solution is except for but you're you're saying that people that have a wrench
the people that have the the main
problem is
People that have a wrench can can see us even if we block them and they have a problem with us
so
Well, you know, I don't know if you want me to name names, but I know maybe I don't think that's true
Because I block myself and I can't see myself when I write so and I got a red
So I just wanted to test the theory out once and I did so yeah
I don't think that's the only the only new mod I've had that you might you might guys might know
That's Hannah and that the reason Hannah has a wrench a standard moderator is because she kept
Getting hit in and stuff like that when you're gonna JT was a mod and
And also, okay, come on, come on. You said it to some bad people. Okay. And so, yeah. And so,
and then also people were coming on under fake accounts of her. And so I need to see the authentic
one. And so, I mean, that's why I did that. I mean, so and it's like, and then she, I don't think
Talking the cat and stuff. So yeah, the talking is the problem the talking the accusations
She has problems with me
and
That's between me and her. It doesn't have anything to do with this channel. Right. She made a puppet of me
She did this she's like as if I did nothing to her as if she did nothing to me
You know, I mean, I know there's other sides to the story and there might be I don't want to come here to fight
That's right. I'm like come here to fight. Yeah, but you're you're there's certain people
That come here that follow me here to slander me in this chat
So what can I do? Yeah
Mm-hmm. Well, if I feel like if I feel like I'm being slandered or text in a chat, you know, I really and it's like well
I'm like, well, why am I in the chat? Okay? Well if I really am a fan of the show and I'm there for the show
I would just maybe go under a different account and just they wouldn't even know it's me and I know can just
I can't get away from them. They know
Have an alias account have an alias account with a different name that they would never even connect it with and this
Just be normal unless you're here to like
If you want to get in the little kerfuffle, I'll try it with you.
But why should she have to do that?
Just to be normal.
That's not fair.
Well
I like the same thing to be normal and talk to people and have decent conversation and
Every chat you go into a bunch of cunts run you out with their stupid nonsense, right?
Okay, it's okay. So Cassie says Hannah was here before your crew. Okay, so Hannah was here
So I don't know if she was followed over here or you know or whatever, okay?
I don't know who's bringing, I know people are posting in public discords and oh come here and
there's you know all these people show up I have no idea who they are they don't care about the show
they're here to like just fight in the chat and stuff like that about stuff I have no idea about
it's just it was just uncomfortable takes away from the show it's not my show and so I mean it's
not the show I want okay this is my show so um I know sometimes you know there's a lesson like
first you know one of her first mods and one of her first member and I got so many
readings from her and then I'm blocked on the account I don't feel it's fair but
you know what am I gonna like you know go cry about it forever now that my
10 accounts are blocked no it's like I give up you know and so maybe that's what
it takes
It's like
No, but okay, but it you know
What you give up? Well, it's like you can be in the chat. It's like you can just ignore the person
I don't I don't know if like why there's the necessary necessity to interact
It's like you are having like it just seems like there's all these attacks going on
It's just I don't know what the history is. I don't really care
It's just not it's just taking away from my show. Okay, and it's like and this is like these are
No
No, I don't think anyone's booked a reading. I don't think anyone's become a member
I don't think anyone is like been supportive like even like supportive really and so
Why am I putting so much energy and time,
taking away from my stuff,
taking away from the time like I'm talking about other stuff,
dealing with this?
Wait a second, wait a second.
Why would we as conscientious observers
support a channel where we feel bullied
and not appreciated?
Why would we make the extra effort?
I wouldn't maybe
You wouldn't but why would you know
I get attacked in the chat by a bunch of funds and then why come then why come over here?
It's like if I'm a cat
It stops it stops my further of investment because
of the people that are coming here and harassing me.
Hi.
So I went to beat his channel one day.
I went to beat it like recently.
I went to beat his channel.
And I went to the chat.
And I don't know if I've even typed in the chat, but the chat was just all talk if they're all talking shit about me
They're all like and it's like and beat an hour gone good terms of time
But her chat was all talking shit about me. So I was like, you know what I'm never coming to this chat again
This is unfriendly territory. I'm like, I'm like, I'm not I don't go to any more. I'm gonna just stay in my chat
Now that I'm just yeah
Now that now that I'm focused on my chat, I'm gonna make sure my chat's a safe place
It's like I don't I don't want my chat to turn into those other chats where I feel
um, attacked and unwelcome I went I went here to be a welcoming place and so even if you have differences
It's not the place to to fight about it and do it here. You guys are doing your own personal vendetta of stuff
I have nothing to do with all on my show
It's no it won't affect anybody. I mean, I will piss those people off enough to like try to privacy strike or
Or flag the channel, but it won't do any won't fix your relationship with them
You know, I I can't fix your relationship with them. And so what I'm just supposed to like
Constantly beyond edge and like, you know, this this makes the show not fun
And what it's like basically and then they did they laughed if the panel gets taken down
They they cheery back say they're cheering backstage people can see them
Everyone's backstage after the show and and it ends. They cheer. They're like yay. We took the no
I'm there. You know, I'm there. I'm there calling everything
Well, so how about that? Yeah, they're really if they're malicious like that
Like why have them on the show or in the chat like I mean, it's like
Mr. Slick
Yes, Amanda. Yes. Good. Good morning by the way. Good morning. Good morning. Hey, I've been
Yeah, hey, I've been gone for a couple of days. So
You know, my only issue with JT is the the avatars
changing the things it shouldn't be
And then when I've touched people out in the past, he always reduces it.
So that's an issue.
What if I don't like Trump?
What if I don't like Donald Trump and I complain about your picture?
Take that picture down. You're not Donald Trump.
Whatever the fuck whoever the fuck dad is a public. He's a public figure. He's not a private figure
I'm talking about people's personal protected HIPAA stuff with their medical, you know pictures of people's cancer scars
I think that's a little different
Sure, but it's a bad case. It's bad case to be reposting it. Excuse me
Does that get you a right to post it?
right to take it
That shows you as a piece of shit person
She put the picture up.
It has to be among one of the worst excuses
I've ever heard in my life.
She put the picture up for herself.
That's like the A-time you said it now.
So are people's Facebook?
No, we all can hear you.
I get it.
We all get it, and still think it's
a shitty, stupid fucking reason.
I can speak for myself, for the others, anything.
Get it. She puts a picture.
Yeah, you don't get it, guys.
Don't you get it?
She put the picture up.
Nobody else speaks for me.
But but but Mr. X, Mr. X,
she put the pitch up.
The pitch up.
You guys are acting like we made it up a picture of Hannah's
Are you having a stroke right now
Fucking stupid beef with pictures on the avatar when you're sitting there with a picture of Donald
Trump and I got a picture to share. You think this is me? No, this is share
The other honey, okay, just take a break for a minute. Let me finish talking to site
Okay, those were my only issues with JT. Otherwise, you know, I don't I don't talk to JT or Goddy or any of them
Really, you know, I'm not over here that much
You know, because sometimes it's in chaotic. I don't have to deal with it. Yeah
And that's what a lot of people are feeling. It's like they they they're like, oh, what's going on in the chat
I don't want to be there and it's like and then there's like no the numbers drop way down and then
People are all unhappy in the chat and it's not any topic that I want to be discussing and it's just keeps going and going
And so it's like it's no it's has to end and it's like it's okay. I understand it was
It's rusty. I understand. Yes. Okay. She posted a photo of that, you know on maybe
Maybe it was a public Facebook, maybe it was private, I don't know how the photo got a hold of, but that's her photo.
And she's a private figure. You're not supposed to go take up the photo of someone's Facebook and post it everywhere.
And that's considered doxing.
So, hang on a second. I want to ask a question. I want to ask people the right to exploit it,
and put it everywhere though. Yes, it does. But that is the way it works on YouTube.
No, it isn't. No, it isn't. It's not allowed. If I came up and somebody takes a picture of me
and they do it all damn day I get told I'm fat I'm ugly my scars somebody told me I got hit
in the head with a shovel one time oh lord yes yeah yeah no it's okay it's okay that's how it works
here but that's how it works it it shouldn't be but it does that's what it's it's
Yeah, it's literally against the toss and it's totally up to the person who hosts the panel
No one would ever talk to you that way on my panel. It would never happen
Yeah
Who cares if you fucking then fuck off if you talk if you don't care then fuck off
If I'm saying who cares whose pictures if you don't like the rules here, and you don't like the people here
And you don't like the guy setting the rules then fuck off to fuck off
Get on a fuck off machine and go fuck off
I've always told you to talk, do what you want to do.
Just about me, because I feel like I've talked the least.
Well, she keeps interrupting.
I don't know what you want me to do.
Oh, we're all on the panel.
Are we going to take turns?
Teacher here, is there a little hand?
Put my hand up to talk.
I love how this lady openly doubles down on being a horrible person.
No manners and no regard whatsoever, and that's like you're it's your manner of argumentation, too
It's like you don't understand. I can do whatever the fuck I want to do
Like you're making some kind of pro argument for it. It's amazing. I don't think I've ever met anybody quite like that
What I was saying dickhead shut up. Well, they talk if you talk shit to people
You're gonna get you're doing right now. You're gonna get your picture taken and they're gonna use it
Period you guys send me a picture of you, and I'm gonna use it now because you just talk shit to me
You can't do that. Yeah, you can do that, and that's what people do
It's about me shouldn't I respond to this like
Yeah. Can somebody pass JT the talking stick? Jesus Christ. Yeah, no. Like I said, whatever your rules are, your rules, right?
You're allowed to make whatever rules you want to, even if people don't like it, right? I get that. That's fine.
In the initially why did it before I even knew the rules or any that? Yeah, the person sitting there talking shit to me
Yeah, that's how I handle that. I'm not gonna sit there and talk shit to them
I'm just gonna put their picture up once you said I couldn't do that. I didn't do it anymore
So it really has been a moot point. I think plus I don't have a wrench so I can't really do that anyway
Yeah, I can't do I can't post links or anything. So what if people are people are gonna say shit about me? Yeah
I have that I'm gonna respond to it. Well the way I responded was against your rules. So I stopped doing it right, right?
Okay, simple. Yeah, I brought with that. I just my my only thing is the rules should apply to everybody equally
I don't think they do and anybody that posts somebody I get somebody else post the salmon
I just end in the stream because he said
I didn't even know if it was a name or it was, but it's like, I'm like, I'm like, I just don't want names or pictures of other people being shown.
It's like, there's no docking in the rules.
That's fair enough to have those rules. And I'm not against you having rules. I don't even if I don't like it.
Can you let him up, Pine?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
No problem. Thank you.
I'm in the show. I'm in the show. I'm in the show. I'm back.
Thank you, Amanda. Hi. You're welcome. I knew you just didn't see it. Yeah, you were
Conversation I didn't mind I didn't mind us. I was just writing like ain't complaining. I just wrote it once
I'm in the back. That's it. Now. I thought yeah, I mean to answer why I did any of that
Yeah, I was responding to things being said about me first and once it was once you made it clear that's against your rules
I didn't do it again. So
Yeah, yeah, it's like I just don't want to be like, you know
I don't want your whole channel to be about me. Jesus Christ, I know I know you're making it out. You're making it about you
No, no, no, I'm not make wait wait wait, please. I'm not making it about me
Do you think I want my channel to be about you?
Do you think I want to be like having like hours long discussions about doxing and and uh, and people's like, you know
cancer scars and
Maybe handling this my show all the time like it's been the last four days. Okay
I want to be like spending all my time on the show talking about this shit. Okay. No, I don't and it's
It was the guy with the long beard that was that the guy was it the other day I was him in the video
Yeah, okay. Yeah, that's y'all's daughter
That's why he's very upset. He they were sitting there almost in tears
You see the interview where he was with his his wife she looked completely
You let them come up here and fucking talk about me so I really could come after you for that
But you let me up here to defend myself
Those people came here to
First of all, first of all,
I don't know what they're doing.
Yeah, they did.
We didn't even know about you.
On Psyche's defense, we didn't even know about you.
But the guy thought he was talking about you.
Yeah, yeah, and shut up
because you know you're telling the truth.
Shut up, he's telling the truth.
Shut up, he's telling the truth, right?
Come on, get out of here.
You let those people up here to fucking attack me.
No, can I speak to them?
You let those people up here to attack me.
I don't know you know exactly that's what I'm saying. Did I have a freak out? No, I'm telling you now
I'm telling you now. I let that all go by because you let me up here to defend myself
So I said nothing else. I did my own stream about it and then that was it
But you're seeing well, they're up here in tears
Next is crazy rusty is crazy
No, I normally I normally don't yell on the panel
I know you rusty. You crazy that I ain't that's I'm not crazy. Okay. I don't worry. Well, we're gonna make the content
You know that oh, yeah, I got all y'all niggas one by one
Mm-hmm
Yeah
I got these people on the pressure now
Yo, John
You used to date Ziggie Ziggie was your yeah your e-boyfriend
The fact that you know that is weird
Did you know that is queer
You mentioned it
Oh
People were stankin
the
It's a battle, I am.
It's so huge.
Sike, would you agree that whenever the fuck I do on my channel pretty much has nothing
to do with this channel?
I mean, I think we could both agree.
Challenge this channel.
Do your thing.
it's
the
Nobody want to be like you. You were
Complaining about the
All right, you're not a model more start complaining that's it move on
There's a lot of people still bitchin about what I'm doing. Hey, you're still talking. They're gonna move on
We don't fucker you you're not listening. You're nobody
Exactly
I don't like it I don't like it if I can't say it with the heart are you
It doesn't matter, it doesn't matter, it does not matter, it's a word, you have to check
my skin color before I use a word, you have to check my skin color before I use a word.
Yeah, no problem.
It's a psych.
Oh, thank you, I hope everybody was getting their screen shots.
So sorry.
Who's that psych?
Hold on, who is that?
Oh, yeah, okay. Oh, so it's like you got a motherfucker in there saying that I'm in the kids and that's cool though, right?
Nobody said nobody said you like them
You crying again
Shut the fuck up you bitch.
Nobody say you like them.
They're not gonna do anything.
Shut up.
Shut the fuck up.
Who said you like mine?
Shut up you little fucking cunt.
Shut the fuck up you cunt.
He's not saying it.
You're saying it.
You're the one saying it.
Is that what your mind goes?
Shut up.
Go toast the toes nose to nose. That's weird, bro
Hey, whatever the fuck you want
No, no, no, and you're saying words. I told you not to say okay, so
Right. No, no, he said the f a gg ot
No, that was JT he don't
You don't I told you know you're on the I'd let you on the panel to explain yourself and you have to
Nigga go go go fuck your girl, bro. You don't like you though. I know that go fuck. Yeah, whatever the
Look at you giggling like a little bitch
Go cook some content papa go go giggle like a little bitch on your channel. That's what you do best, right?
I could go like a little faggot much.
Wow, there.
Bye. Bye, JT.
And how do you take there?
And that was purposely because we just talked about it.
So that was purpose.
And so you are banned from the show, JT.
You know, I did this in the first place, Amanda.
You had to shoot your big fat gullet.
The show, I'm ending the stream.
Bye. No, I don't.